baby I Like It Raw raw Advantage likes
it raw baby I Like It Raw yeah baby I
like it
ra what's up everybody this is Batman
filling in for Chris of the raw
advantage today I want to get you a
super freaking rwome recipe a Cravings
Buster me have it
now I'm in party mode and what goes
better with parties than tacos let's
jump into some hard shell tacos ha now
for this recipe you're going to need six
cobs of fresh corn eight Tomatoes a
bunch of green onions 1/4 cup flax seed
and eigh a cup of mixed spices see the
description below powerful blender
preferably the Vitamix plus Excalibur
trays with teflex sheets and the
almighty Excalibur dehydrator five now
at the r spe you like my Speedos don't
you well let's get cracking on this
recipe first cut your Coba corn in and
then take all the kernels
off damn you got a lot of
corn well that doesn't work cut your
Tomatoes throw the tomatoes and corn in
the
blender dump the flax and spices in the
blender fill corn to the top and place
on the almighty Vitamix
chassell one of the things that makes
the vitamic so awesome is the exclusive
tamper you want to have it ready
[Music]
want to blend it till it's really nice
and
smooth now that's pretty darn nice and
smooth but we don't want to forget the
green onions so we add those last to
retain a bit of
texture and there you have it we're done
and ready to spread them out this recipe
made seven cups take a half2 cup
measuring
cup place it on one
corner take another half2
cup place it on
another smooth it out a little
bit and then use a
knife carefully thin it into your
shape you can fix it the
edges shape it exactly how you like and
repeat play with thickness find out what
works best for you I like him a little
thinner and
crunchy Place him in the Excalibur food
dehydrator you can fit as many as four
tacos from a
sheet the manual says you can put them
up to 150 for the first hour to 2 hours
for turning them down to 105 to 110 so
now we just leave it until we need to
check it turn them and flip them
turn it down to 105 to
110 roll up a tlex sheet and fold two
shells over the sheet you can fit up to
four shells per sheet put them all in
the
dehydrator stack them shells like a boss
yeah if you're storing the shells put
them in a Ziploc bag and suck all the
air out for extra freshness and there
you have it you have a whole bunch of
perfectly dehydrated crispy formed taco
shells I hope you guys absolutely enjoy
these for more ideas of fillings check
out my TR Retreat treats book in the
Mexican section let's check out what
everyone thinks oh naturally Ashley's
making four tacos look pretty they're
all ready and done what do you think I
think they look really nice oh my gosh
wow oh what do you got there
Kurt hot sauce Ashley's famous cheese
sour cream more cheese salsa mock meat
Jacob ra vegan taco night
yay
y oh damn that looks like a pretty good
taco
there does it taste like a taco tastes
like a taco tast like a good taco too
nice
[Applause]
yay so here's the super tacon and the
Aly I'm glad you bit it away from me so
I just got a nice back ofier head you
like my head you like my head there you
go check out how good this
is do you like my head oh Chris giv good
head
shots there we go Dog Night
forever
yay well there you have it Ro taco night
I hope you guys like the recipe enjoy it
and check out the playlist below for a
lot more free rwome recipes so uh if you
want some good filling recipes for this
check out the ti Retreat treats book
down here what the hell is my bad family
doing you guys are
badad special Thanks goes out to Batman
for hooking this recipe up for us pretty
damn nice like that Batman guy see you
guys next time enjoy
love raw taco shells
these taco shells ain't no joke
[Music]
fo check out this video on the making of
the infamous banana
tattoo also don't forget to click for
your free
Ebu excited to announce my new iPhone
app free with 101 frecking rossom
recipes teror Retreat treats food
combining charge shopping carts and more